flypeach.com 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy | Peach Aviation

Peach Aviation Limited (referred to below as “Peach Aviation”) complies with the Act on the Protection of Personal Information and related laws, and appropriately handles personal information we receive from our customers (information about living persons consisting of names, dates of birth, or other information that could be used to identify individuals) (referred to below as “Personal Information”) as outlined below. 

### 1\. Purpose of collecting Personal Information and Retained Personal Data

All or part of the Personal Information and Retained Personal Data may be used within the scope necessary for the following purposes:

[1] Reservations, ticket sales, check-in, airport service handling, and in-flight services with regard to air transport services  
[2] Reservations, ticket sales, and airport handling for interline transportations, joint operations, code share, intermodal transportations and contract operations  
[3] Peach Express membership enrollment and customer data handling related to facilitating day-to-day management of said program.   
[4] COMOMO enrollment and customer data handling related to facilitating day-to-day management of said program  
[5] tabinoco enrollment and customer data handling related to facilitating day-to-day management of said program  
[6] Information, information provision and management concerning the above articles [1] - [5] and other services or products offered by Peach Aviation (hereinafter collectively referred to as "services, etc.") various events, prizes, competitions, and campaigns (hereinafter referred to as "events etc.")   
[7] All operations incidental or related to articles [1] - [6] above.   
[8] Creating statistical data processed into a format that shall not identify individuals in relation to the services, events, etc.   
[9] Management and notification of services, products, events and campaigns of Peach Aviation Group companies and partner companies.  
[10] Responses to inquiries and requests  
[11] Sales of property insurance, small-amount short-term insurance and their associated services for which Peach Aviation is contracted by ACE Insurance, Sompo Japan Nipponkoa Insurance Inc., and Ticket Guard Small Amount & Short Term Insurance Co., Ltd.

Note: For more details about the purposes for which these insurance companies use personal information, please visit their websites.

-ACE Insurance  
( <http://www.ace-insurance.co.jp/privacy.html> )  
-Sompo Japan Nipponkoa Insurance Inc.  
( <http://www.sjnk.co.jp/private_information/> )  
-Ticket Guard Small Amount & Short Term Insurance Co., Ltd.  
( <https://www.ticketguard.jp/company_003.html> ) 

### 2\. Collection of personal information

Peach Aviation will obtain Personal Information only by fair and appropriate means.

### 3\. Provision to third parties

Peach Aviation will not provide Personal Information to any third parties except under the following circumstances or for the following purposes. Please note that when Personal Information is provided to or shared with contractors to whom Peach Aviation entrusts operations, this is not considered “provision to third parties.”

[1] Customer consent has been obtained.  
[2] Provision is required by laws or regulations.  
[3] Provision is required to protect human life, health, or property in cases where obtaining customer consent is difficult.  
[4] Provision is required to cooperate with the public affairs of national or local governments, and when obtaining customer consent is likely to hinder the administration of public affairs.  
[5] Personal Information is provided in a format that does not disclose identity, as in statistical data.  
[6] Personal Information is provided as a result of the succession of business due to a merger, company split, transfer of business or otherwise. 

### 4\. Trust of Personal Information to trustees and supervision of third parties

When the need arises, Peach Aviation entrusts work to trustees, and in such cases, may entrust to handle Personal Information within the scope of what is required to achieve the purpose of utilization. In such cases, Peach Aviation appropriately supervises trustees, including concluding contracts governing utilization of Personal Information. 

### 5\. Data sharing

Peach Aviation may share Personal Information with joint users of this information as follows.

[1]  
-Scope of data sharing  
My Theater, Inc.  
-Items to be shared  
Customer name, address, telephone and fax numbers, e-mail address, age, the date of birth, nationality, airline ticket purchase record -Purpose of use  
1) To judge whether or not video delivery services operated by the third party (referred to below as “video delivery services”) fulfill the required conditions when utilized by customers  
2) To carry out market research and data analysis for the purpose of researching and developing new products and services related to video delivery services operated by the third party  
3) For notification of new products and services related to video delivery services, by direct mail, etc., and other services related to video delivery services  
4) In the event of an inquiry, application for use or other request from a customer regarding products and services provided by the third party as a part of its video delivery service operations  
Party responsible for management of Personal Information  
Peach Aviation Limited. Method of obtaining Personal Information  
Website, telephone and fax, mail, in person at airport counter etc. 

### 6\. Managing Personal Information

We take all appropriate and necessary measures to prevent leakage, loss, or damage of Personal Information, and exert ourselves to keep Personal Information accurate and up-to-date within the scope of utilization and ensure that our executives and employees are properly trained regarding appropriate handling to safeguard the security of Personal Information. An appropriate retention period for Personal Information is established separately in accordance with the purpose for which such information is used. Following the expiration of this period, we dispose of the Personal Information by appropriate methods. 

### 7\. Inquiries and submission of requests for disclosure of Retained Personal Data

(1) Notification of the purpose of utilization, disclosure, correction, deletion, addition, discontinuance, and erasure of Retained Personal Data  
Any customer request for the notification of the purpose of use, the disclosure, the correction, deletion, addition, discontinuance of utilization or erasure of Retained Personal Data held by Peach Aviation (referred to below as “Disclosure etc.”) shall be handled, within the scope of relevant laws and regulations, after requests for Disclosure etc. are determined to authentically originate with the customer or his or her proxy.

However, we remind customers that requests for Disclosure etc. may impede the provision of services to the customer, despite our best intentions. Also, in some cases it may not be possible under the relevant regulations to fulfill requests for discontinuance of utilization or erasure.

**request guidelines**   
(1) Address to send requests for Disclosure, etc.  
Any customer request for Disclosure, etc. must be made using the specified forms, accompanied by the necessary documents, and received by mail at the following address: *Please note that we are unable to respond to any requests submitted by means other than postal mail.

Personal Information Desk  
Peach Aviation Limited  
1 Senshu-kuko-naka Tajiri-cho, Sennan-gun, Osaka 549-0011, Japan

(2) Documents required for the request for Disclosure etc.  
Any request for Disclosure, etc. must be submitted by post after downloading request forms (A) and filling out all required information, enclosing personal identification documents (B), and enclosing a self-addressed, stamped envelope (C) and a fee (when the request is for disclosure or for notification of purpose of use only) (D). Please note that handling of requests received from customers living outside Japan may differ, so please inquire with the Personal Information Desk at the address listed below. Customer requests for Disclosure, etc. may not be acknowledged if any of the required information is missing.

(A) Request form   
   Form requesting Disclosure, etc. of Retained Personal Data:(  PDF)   
(B) Personal identification documents   
Please enclose either (1) or (2) below.  
(1) A copy of one of the following: driver's license, passport, physical disability certificate, resident card or special permanent resident certificate.  
(2) Instead of the documents listed in (1) it is possible to submit two of the following:  
Copy of health insurance certificate  
Copy of pension booklet  
Original certificate of seal registration (issued no more than three months ago) with registered seal stamped in the margin  
(C) Self-addressed stamped envelope   
Please write your name and address on the envelope and affix an 82-Japanese yen stamp.  
(D) Fee: A fee of 1,000 Japanese yen will be charged for each request (when the request is for disclosure or for notification of purpose of use only).   
Please enclose a 1,000-Japanese yen postal money order issued by Japan Post Bank. *If the enclosed fee in insufficient or if no fee is enclosed, you will receive a written notification of this. If payment is not received within two weeks after the notification is issued, your request for Disclosure, etc. will be deemed unreceived.

(3) When request for Disclosure, etc. is sent by a representative  
When the legal representative of a minor (under 20 years of age) or adult ward requests Disclosure, etc., or the person in question delegates a representative to request Disclosure, etc. on his or her behalf, in addition to the documents for the person him or herself, listed in paragraph (2) above, please enclose the two following types of documents relating to the representative.  
1)Identification documents of representative (same as those listed in item 2(B) above)  
2) Power of attorny, or other document certifying the right of the representative to request Disclosure, etc.

(4) Way of responses to requests for Disclosure, etc.  
A written response will be sent to the individual who requested disclosure (i.e. to the address on the self-addressed stamped envelope.) When information is not to be disclosed, you will be informed of this fact and the reason. Responses may take several days to arrive. Thank you for your understanding. Please note that Retained Personal Data will not be disclosed under the following circumstances:  
(A) Identity of requesting party cannot be verified  
(B) Request is made through a representative, and identity of representative cannot be verified  
(C) Not all required documents are enclosed  
(D) Information for which disclosure is requested does not fit the definition of “Personal Information”  
(E) Disclosure would run the risk of adverse effects to the safety, wellbeing, property or other rights and interests of the requesting party or a third party  
(F) Disclosure would have the potential to interfere significantly with business operations of Peach Aviation  
(G) Disclosure would violate other laws and regulations

(5) Purpose of use of Personal Information obtained in relation to requests for Disclosure, etc.  
Personal information obtained as a result of requests for Disclosure, etc. will be utilized only within the scope necessary for response to the request. Documents received will be kept for a designated length of time and then disposed of by appropriate means.

(2) Other Inquiries  
Please send all inquiries regarding handling of Personal Information to the following address. All inquiries should be made by post. Thank you for your cooperation.

Personal Information Desk   
Peach Aviation Limited  
1 Senshu-kuko-naka Tajiricho, Osaka,  
Japan 549-0011 

### 8\. Application and modification of this Privacy Policy

Use of Peach Aviation services and products by a customer is deemed to constitute full understanding of and consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Please note that this Privacy Policy is subject to revision by Peach Aviation at any time. 

January 26, 2016 

## How we deal with Personal Information on our website

The following describes how we treat personal information gathered via the Peach Aviation Limited (referred to below as “Peach Aviation”) website and app(the “Peach Aviation website”). If you wish to know more about our general policy on privacy protection, please refer to the separate document entitled “Privacy Policy.” 

### 1\. Introduction

This document defines how we deal with information gathered via the Peach Aviation website and is based on the Peach Aviation Privacy Policy. Peach Aviation makes every effort to protect your privacy so that you can use the Peach Aviation website with confidence and peace of mind. By using the Peach Aviation website you are deemed to have understood and agreed to the following content. 

### 2\. Scope

In order to provide useful information and services to the customer, links to other websites are posted on the Peach Aviation website, but this Privacy Policy does not apply to sites accessed via such links. If you access websites administered by third parties, we recommend that you check the privacy protection policies of each individual website. 

### 3\. Security

Protection of personal information is secured through security technology based on SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) (*1) data encryption. This means that any information you provided when using this website cannot be accessed by an unauthorized third party. Furthermore, a firewall, anti-virus measures, and other measures deemed effective have been installed to prevent disclosure, appropriation, alteration, etc., of personal information by unauthorized third parties. 

*1 About SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption  
With SSL encryption, before customers’ personal information is transmitted, an electronic dialogue (digital authentication / digital signature) takes place between the customer and Peach Aviation, and two-way authentication is achieved before data is sent. During transmission, data is scrambled with random numerals, preventing data from mistakenly reaching third parties who may attempt to steal it.

In addition, data is encrypted using a method that combines two types of encryption methods; public key encryption (RSA) and symmetric key encryption (private key cryptography). An electronic “key” is required to decipher this information. Even if information is intercepted by third parties, it is impossible to decrypt encrypted information without the correct key. Although the number of available keys is finite, it is extremely difficult for third parties to decrypt information as it requires an unrealistically long time, even if work is conducted computationally using a computer, etc., to find the right key by testing all keys in turn. 

### 4\. Collection of data

[1] Site access  
When customers access our website, we collect data in the form of cookies (*2) and mobile device Individual Identification Numbers (*3), in order to provide the information below to third parties so that our customers can use our website with greater ease.  
\- Registration data from special campaigns  
\- Site access history (using Web beacon) (*4)  
Customer can block receipt of cookies at any time by changing the Internet browser setting. However, please note that without using cookies, response speed may go down significantly.

[2] E-mail  
When we send mail to our customers, the following data may be collected:  
-The status of HTML e-mails, i.e., whether they have been opened or previewed (using Web beacons)  
\- Whether our website has been accessed via a link in a text e-mail or HTML mail. 

*2 Cookies A technology the user’s computer employs to remember that the user made access to our website. Information collected using cookies cannot be used to specify individual identity, such as the e-mail address or name of users. Peach Aviation shall be able to provide third parties with information collected by cookies within the scope necessary to fulfill the purposes stipulated in [Usage of Cookies and Individual Identification Numbers of Mobile Phones] Note that when customers access our website using cookies, it shall be deemed that the customer acknowledges the right of Peach Aviation to utilize the information that the customer accessed our website.

*3 Individual identification number  
A unique identification number for a mobile phone, based on the mobile phone number.

*4 Web beacon  
Minute pictures invisible to the naked eye (1x1 pixel GIFs) that are embedded into Web pages or HTML e-mails and used to collect information on when the page or e-mail has been viewed. Web beacons record data on the opening / previewing of e-mails and access to websites. 

January 26, 2016
